The greater the legend, the harder the fall.
Paterno is a drama, tv movie film directed by Barry Levinson.
After becoming the winningest coach in college football history, Joe Paterno is embroiled in Penn State's Jerry Sandusky sexual
abuse scandal, challenging his legacy and forcing him to face questions of institutional failure regarding the victims.
Joe Paterno, played by Al Pacino.
Sue Paterno, played by Kathy Baker.
MRI Tech, played by Kenneth Maharaj.
Guido D'Elia, played by Michael Mastro.
Bobby - Media Wrangler, played by Joshua Morgan.
Sports Producer, played by Ross Degraw.
Paterno is a 2018 American television drama film directed by Barry Levinson.
It stars Al Pacino as former Penn State football coach Joe Paterno, and his career leading up
to his dismissal following the university's child sex abuse scandal in 2011.
Riley Keough, Kathy Baker, Greg Grunberg and Annie Parisse also star.
The film premiered on HBO on April 7, 2018.
The tone is emotional.